{"data":[{"question":"I heard that you had bought that house and be moved there before you got your promotion.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"heard","b":"had bought","c":"be moved","d":"got","answer":"3","explain":"- Be moved-> moved","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"We had no sooner left the house when it began to rain.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"no sooner","c":"when","d":"began","answer":"3","explain":"- When-> than\nno sooner had\/did ... than","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Never to put off until tomorrow what you can do today.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Never","b":"to put","c":"until","d":"what","answer":"2","explain":"- To put-> putting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"My father is tired of living in the city although he wants to live in a quiet village.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"tired","b":"of","c":"although","d":"to live","answer":"3","explain":"- Although-> because","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"She went to the dentist because she got an toothache.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"went","b":"because","c":"got","d":"an toothache","answer":"4","explain":"- An toothache-> toothache","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Jeremy invents frequently ridiculous stories like that.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"frequently","b":"ridiculous","c":"stories","d":"like","answer":"1","explain":"- Frequently-> frequently invents","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Although Bob didn't speak Dutch, he decided settling in Amsterdam.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Although","b":"didn't speak","c":"decided","d":"settling","answer":"4","explain":"- Settling-> to settle","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Without for this treatment, the patient would have died.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Without","b":"for","c":"patient","d":"would have died","answer":"2","explain":"- For-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The farmers are simply trying to fatten the animals in order that obtain a higher price on the market.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"simply","b":"to fatten","c":"in order that","d":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- In order that-> in order to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"John asked Oliver if she could remember what she had put the camera.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"asked","b":"if","c":"could","d":"what","answer":"4","explain":"- What-> where","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}